(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T05:38:19.660966",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I ain’t trying to stress you, I must confess though
My heart’s beating to your song
Thinking hurry up Orpheus, time’s a wasting
Show me what you really wanna do!
Another late night, aimless dreaming
The day to day starts to call
Still got like a million deadlines
Hey you got eyes and ears, but you don't look or listen
In other words you're useless, every last one of ya
And that's why I'm gonna send you all to hell
声援背負い 颯爽と登場
Cheered on, stepping up with dashing ease
I'm just the type you'd forget, so don't waste your time
千切れ 腐りかけの chain, going insane
Frayed, half-rotting chain, going insane
朽ち果てたような世界で 深く重ねた光
In a decaying world, lights piled deep
脈打つ鼓動 誰にも 誰にも
A throbbing heartbeat, to no one, to no one
言葉を紡いでよ
Weave words
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
逃そう 逃がすまい 未来の慈悲
Let's not let it escape, mercy of the future
見えないサインをおくれよ
Give me an unseen sign
もっとって
And even more...
Tell me what I'm to not say
What's your problem?
孤独を一人 私が迷う
Lonely and alone, I wander
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
巡る巡る
Revolving, revolving
運命に逆らって 出会い想いを通わせた
Defying fate, we met and connected our feelings
The strangers I followed with stars in my eyes
So you keep on waiting, wanting, faking you're someone
You're not reaching, longing, changing for someone
I can't be someone else
Despite it all my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still in my heart...
暗くなる頃 始まるパーティー 集まる人種は鵺々
The party starts as it gets dark, a mysterious crowd gathers
Flash bang
In this moment, maybe it's hopeless
I can see stars now, running through an endless sky
夢を見るたび 生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
Every time I dream, I end up thinking about why I was born
Ah,美しい青い日々だな
Ah, what a beautiful blue days
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
What's up all you deadbeats?
Welcome to Disastershow!
リリースよ行こうぜ
Release your ghost out!
You got eyes and ears but you don't look or listen
And that's why I'm gonna send you all to hell
声援背負い 颯爽と登場
Cheered on, stepping up with dashing ease
I'm just the type you'd forget, so don't waste your time
Somebody's gotta pay while I live with the pain
思いがつのる場所に花は咲く
Flowers bloom where feelings grow strong.
枯れない...
They won't wither...
Let's try it
傷だらけの希望を 爪が立てる胸で
In my heart, where my claws dig into scarred hope
痛んだって気付かれたってキャラじゃない 本来
It's not my style to show pain or be noticed, normally.
傷付くこと恐れず 傷付いて食い破るわ
Without fearing scars, I get hurt and tear through it.
誰だ一体 誰だ一体 誰だ一体 どうしてもこの理想は 無理だろうって
Who on earth, who on earth, who on earth says this ideal is impossible?
誰が一体 どうしても 譲れないってことさ
Whoever says it, I won't back down no matter what.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
世界が世界の尺度だってだって
The world's scale is just the world's scale.
そんなとこどこ取りそうも語ってら
Talking about such things...
Minna minna's problems, everybody's got 'em
Everyone's got their problems...
And you can't never keep it satisfied until somebody's at the bottom
And you can never be satisfied until someone's at the bottom.
心が叫ぶよ
My heart cries out,
時に楽しくが
Sometimes joyfully,
飛ぶ稲妻のように 激しく生きるんだ
Living as fiercely as a flying lightning bolt.
俺が通る今すぐに どけ
Get out of my way right now as I pass!
Let's try it
傷だらけの希望を 爪が立てる胸で
In my heart, where my claws dig into scarred hope
痛んだって気付かれたってキャラじゃない 本来
It's not my style to show pain or be noticed, normally.
傷付くこと恐れず 傷付いて食い破るわ
Without fearing scars, I get hurt and tear through it.
誰だ一体 誰だ一体 誰だ一体 どうしてもこの理想は 無理だろうって
Who on earth, who on earth, who on earth says this ideal is impossible?
誰が一体 どうしても 譲れないってことさ
Whoever says it, I won't back down no matter what.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
譲れないってことさ
I won't back down.
皆さん
Everyone!
We're just getting started!
始まったね
It's begun.
Ten beats!
Places they shake, 'cause I take control
Like primal waves above where we all go
Is it glory you're after like me? Underestimated everywhere I turn
Taking aim, but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
You're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure,
there'll be no one to save
Where is your pride?
Yeah, human will to survive
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is delusion and decay
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals,
we're not equals
you're just confused
Base instincts take control
Like primal ways of a warrior
Is it glory you're after, like me?
Underestimated everywhere I turn
Taking aim, but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
You're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
Hidden motivation, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Let me ignite you
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure, there'll be no one to save
Where is your pride? Yeah, human will to survive
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is delusion and decay
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals, we're not equals
We're not rivals, you're just confused
Lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
So, go ahead and run up on me 'til you get your shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding, come on, ready or not
Another life and you would never give a second thought
Thinking your pride's different than mine
Ticking all your vital signs off
But we still gotta protect all our friends from our enemies
Wouldn't you agree? Ha!
Thank you for coming today, everyone!
It's over!
It's okay. No, no, no,
we're back, we're back.
Just some technical difficulties.
Staff's on the beats.
Everyone, calm down.
It's fine, it's fine.
We're- we're okay.
Welcome, welcome!
Hey, you know what?
It fits in the theme of the show
that there'd be some technical issues.
So it can't be perfect, right?
But I'm looking at your comments right now.
And thank you, by the way, to Shiou-de for the raid as well.
Hope the outfit reveal went super good.
Hi, Deadbeats! Hello!
We're here! We're here!
We're finally at the Disaster Peace venue!
And I'm reading your comments, but there might be a little bit of lag,
so sorry about that.
Anyway, check it out.
I've got my own special mic that is definitely what I'm using to talk
and not the headset.
But check it out, I'll show it to you closer later.
Oh, hello, Liz is here too!
Amazing senpai, woooo!
Thank you!
Welcome to Disaster Show, everyone!
Disaster Peace is out at long last!
Hooray, we did it!
We finally got here!
And now I'm going to do some songs for you guys.
Wow, Akas- I can't read it right now, but I'll have to read them later.
Thank you so much!
The new art style is so nice.
This is some unreal power, Deadbeats, unreal power!
It's stunning, isn't it?
I bet you want to get a closer look...
おいします
Oishimasu...
Hey, hey! Hold on,
I think this is my normal hand. Oh.
All right, I'm going to take some—
I'm going to get some good reactions for you guys. Hold on a second.
Here I go. Check this— check this shit out.
Whoa!
I'm being silly 'cause I need time to chill right now.
You sound amazing. I'm doing my best!
And the outfit, too.
Look at how shiny!
Shiny.
It just looks so good.
And my face? My face looks good, too.
Oh gosh, I'm still not used to holding the camera, though, so I'm trying to make it perfect.
But I might have to edit things a little bit— you might have to edit it later.
Hold on, no, I got this. Okay.
RTX on.
Very realist.
I can wink. Hold on. Here— here I go. Here, wait, hold— hold on.
I— I got this. I suck at this.
That's okay, though. That's okay. It's fine if it's not perfect.
I think I can wink. Check this out. Ganbatte!
Close enough.
It looks good. And look, behind us, we've got the track...
from the Let's Just Crash MV, and we've got Challenger's car behind me.
And we've also got King's car as well.
Um, and then, well, you Deadbeats, you're all on your way to the next stage, so you're not there yet.
Um, but let me show you my mic. My... mic miseru kara.
Okay, check it out. Check out the mic. This is the special Mori Calliope mic...
that was made specially from...
Isn't it cool?
Look at how sick! The red and the roses, I'm obsessed.
I'm obsessed with it.
So anyway, that's what's going on, Deadbeats.
It's the actual future of Hololive. Well, I mean, the technology will only get better and better.
So, um, anyway, this is exciting. You guys want to see some more songs?
Also buy the album! I'm all ben out of shape.
I feel like MCs, I'm like good when it's an actual live, like in a venue, but then if it's like this, I screw up a lot.
Oh well, new merch? Uh, not— I mean this— oh, you're talking about the mic? You want the mic as merchandise?
I'll think about it. Not a bad idea. I think P-son's listening to that, so I'll have to talk to her about it later.
Welcome to the future!
Anyway, Deadbeats, I got to do a quick costume change and scene change.
So, let's get out of here and I'll sing some more songs and meet up with you hither and thither— that's probably the wrong word to use in that situation, but thank you, Saf-son!
All right, I'll catch you guys there. Time for a henshin. Ikuzo!
不確かな物語に 勝ち取るはアイデンティティー
In this uncertain story, what we want to win is our identity.
あれやこれやと
Trying this and that,
手を変え品を変え
changing means and methods,
ドキリと胸を刺す情歌
a passion that stabs the chest suddenly.
感情はノンフィクションで
Emotions are non-fiction,
喜怒哀楽
full of joy, anger, sorrow, and pleasure.
一心同体 一切合切の衝動
One body and one mind, every single impulse.
失敗も成功も味わい 我らゴールデンバディ
Taste both failure and success, we are the Golden Buddy.
意味なんてないような世界で 偶然を重ねた光
In a world that seems to have no meaning, a light formed by overlapping coincidences.
脈打つ鼓動 誰にもなれない言葉を紡いでよ
A pulsating heartbeat, weave words that no one else can become.
舐めんなよーよ
Don't underestimate me,
小さな勇気ひとつありゃ十分 強気に行こうぜ高みへと
just one bit of small courage is enough, strongly toward the heights.
圧倒絶頂
Overwhelming, pinnacle,
2人ならやれるさ
if we're together, we can do it.
back-to-back, no matter what
背負ったもん武器に変わる spot
the spot where what we've carried turns into a weapon.
段違い遠くまで飛ばす shout
A different level, a shout that flies far away.
誰も邪魔できねえこの rout
No one can disturb this route.
1等2等3通りってのはなから loser
Talking about 1st, 2nd, 3rd options, you're a loser from the start.
うざいぐらい貪欲に
Greedily to the point of annoyance,
ハート地獄からかっぱらいちまえ
steal your heart back from hell.
loop 輪廻じゃない route は無限に
Not a loop of reincarnation, the route is infinite.
ありふれた道じゃない 荊の道を好む玄人
Not a common path, an expert who prefers the path of thorns.
盛大にもう笑えばいいさ
Just laugh grandly now.
才能煩悩のグラデーション どうせならぐちゃぐちゃにしてよ
A gradation of talent and worldly desires, you'd better make it messy if you're going to do it.
始めたのならやり切る覚悟を 敗者と勝者の duet
If you've started, have the determination to finish it, a duet of losers and winners.
劣等感 弾き出された不条理の屑
Inferiority complex, trash of absurdity that's been ejected,
振り払え貪欲に 志は消えない
greedily shake it off, ambitions never disappear,
2人ならやれるさ
if we're together, we can do it.
生きるってなんだ サボった者勝ちかそんなもの 握りつぶせ
What is living? Is it better to be lazy? Crush such things.
上辺じゃいられない エンタメライダー 人生賭け金駆け抜け 絶頂も栄光も
We can't just remain on the surface, Entertain-Rider. Bet your life and run through, despair and glory too.
lemme see you fight back
どうなったって何にも変わらないんだって
You say that no matter what happens, nothing changes.
ミームされた現実に囚われて this life where we're stuck taking chances
Trapped in a meme-ified reality, this life where we're stuck taking chances.
飽き飽きしてんでしょ？？
You're sick of it, right?
we're living in a world with no direction, reach out with our light 'till we make a connection, tearing the walls apart, facing it all, side by side, once again, it's us against the world
舐めんなよーよ 本能をヒリつかせて
Don't underestimate me, let your instincts burn.
本物見せつけろ 圧倒絶頂
Show me the real deal, overwhelming, pinnacle,
アンバランスを踊れ
dance in the unbalance.
折れるなんて思ったもんな チグハグなもの
Thinking it would break, such mismatched things...
握れ let's goさ 奪い切れ ない
Grab it, let's go, take it all back!
逃さない まだ人生 逆 逆 逆 にさ
Won't let you escape yet, life is going reverse!
絶望も生き残れ ネメシスよ fight back
Survive the despair too, Nemesis, fight back!
どんな痛みに 向かってないんだって
Facing whatever pain comes our way—
見失った現実にとらわれて
trapped in a lost reality—
This life where we stop taking chances 焦り焦り焦りしたんだぜ
getting so impatient in this life where we stop taking chances.
We're living in a world with no direction
Reach out with our words till we make a connection
壊れんのwallsアパート Facing it all side by side
tearing down the walls apart, facing it all side by side.
Once again it's us against the world 今面舵取れよ
Once again it's us against the world, now steer hard!
本当の未来を見つけ出せ ほんものに
Find the true future, make it real,
ざっとさせ 上上 上向いていこう
standing tall, looking up, let's keep going.
踊れ
Dance!
Odore
Odore yeah
See just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I want to see
that view that I want to see—
A place in history that's mine
I don't know why we're always side-by-side but worlds apart
I don't know why we're always side by side, but worlds apart.
It's tried by fire, I'm fighting for a place where we can breathe
When fight ticks over, I might just take it out on you
cuz you're too good to be true, struggling but carrying on
'cause you're too good to be true, struggling but carrying on.
I'll go where nobody is gone
I'll go where nobody has gone,
I'm searching again and again and again for something only I can do
Asking why I can't be someone else, despite it all my mind has become my hell
with no escape, we're hopin' in the dark, but still in my heart
your words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go, but I can't erase you, I'm following behind
but I won't chase you, I'm swallowing my pride until the time that I can face you
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
it's never been enough, but I'll keep on writing a story that's evolving
from the day that I decided I'm alone
I don't belong anywhere anymore, it was my decision
I'm gonna break down the door to your heart without your permission
What if I'd walked away? How can I still carry on?
Someday when you're finally gone, I'm searching again and again and again for something only I can do
Someday when you're finally gone, I'm searching again and again for something only I can do.
The truth is I can't be someone else, despite it all my mind has become my hell
with no escape, we're hopin' in the dark, but still in my heart
my words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go and you can't erase me cuz I'm the only one that could ever replace me
I'm finally letting go and you can't erase me cause I'm the only one that could ever replace me,
igniting every line until the time that I can face me
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting, it's never been enough
but I'll keep on writing a story that evolved me
it's a day that I'm deciding I'm alright
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I want to see, I still could make it in time
皆さん、Welcome to the next stage!
Everyone, welcome to the next stage!
ぽちぽち、Thank you for the ポチポチポチ.
Pochipochi, thank you for the pochipochi!
Thank you so much! What did you guys think? And check it out! We got this up—
and now I'm being goofy, I'm sorry.
ぽちぽちぽち、Thank you so much! Oh, is is is it out? I hear sorry if there's like a again just a lag
Pochipochipochi, thank you so much! Oh, is it out? I hear, sorry if there's again a lag...
broadcast to all of you so there might
be a bit of lag,
Thank you so much, you guys.
Posh, posh, posh. Thank you.
Oh, but we might we might need to refresh the chat
Oh, but we might need to refresh the chat.
because now it has stopped moving. Anyway... Oh wow, I think it just exploded when Rora entered the chat, anyway.
Oh wow, it just exploded when Rora entered.
I hope you guys have been liking the new songs.
Memento is one of the new songs that I wrote. I wish I could go into it in a longer MC,
Memento is one of the new songs that I wrote.
or talk more about it cuz there's so much I want to say about that song.
or talk more about it, because there's so much...
hold on, hold on, I'm frozen in—I'm frozen in place!
Hold on, hold on, I'm frozen in place!
Okay, we're good. We're good. Daijoubu. Sorry, zawarudo. No problem, no problem.
Okay, we're good. Daijoubu. No problem!
Here, for now though, instead of going into talking about the lyrics,
For now though, instead of talking about lyrics
which I'll probably do during the next stream, we'll find some time before or after I play a game, and then I'll talk about the songs.
we'll find time before or after I play a game.
You know, Kenti couldn't be here
for Gold On Balance, but you know what I've learned from Kenti's song is that fan service is very important.
for Gold On Balance, but fan service is important.
I used to be really like nervous about doing some fan service and stuff like that cuz like I'm an embarrassed person.
I used to be really nervous about doing fan service.
But Kenti so easily is just like oh like choo-choo to like the fans like wink and like I don't know he's so good at the fansa and like with no shame whatsoever.
Kenti does it so easily with no shame whatsoever.
I thought to myself, I need to try and do some of that too, so I'm going to do that.
I thought to myself, I need to try that too.
Chu—probably not very good at it, but anyway, chu—hold on, I'll start...
Probably not very good at it, but...
Oh, no, it's perfect because zawarudo—zawarudo, it stopped it for you so that you could get a little picture.
Oh, it's perfect, it stopped it for you to see.
Watch where you're pointing that camera. Hold on a second, I'm not pointing it anywhere suspicious.
Watch where you're pointing that camera!
What are you talking about?
Can I do—can I do a funny face now?
Can I do a funny face now?
Ah! Ha! Oh, no.
Ah... oh no.
Anyway, um, so here's this outfit. And it looks so high quality again.
Anyway, so here's this outfit.
Hey, you notice something about the stage?
Hey, notice something about the stage?
This is the coin from the beginning of Gold On Balance.
This is the coin from Gold On Balance.
Deadbeats, look.
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world where meaning doesn't exist,
不確かな物語に
into an uncertain story...
Um, anyway, so ch- check it out.
Um, anyway, so check it out.
Hold on, look at how cool the stage is, by the way. Are you checking out the stage?
Look at how cool the stage is, by the way.
Look at those the roses the moon it reminds me of um when I debuted from Universal Music Japan
Reminds me of when I debuted in Japan.
and I had the moon in the background of what was it? I think it was one of my debut albums. So cool, looking very respectful.
One of my debut albums. So cool.
Oh, I know. You don't need to tell me. I already know. Of course, as always, I wish I could put it as high as possible.
You don't need to tell me, I already know.
Whoa, my eyes are glowing in the darkness. What about the effects? The effects are also so cool for this show.
The effects are also so cool for this show.
I can't believe it. We have some even more amazing stages coming up. But if you guys haven't checked out the album yet,
If you haven't checked out the album yet,
it's full of brand new songs. Um, one of them I composed myself, and then all the songs all the English in my songs is written by me,
it's full of brand-new songs written by me.
um except for maybe Cold Following, and that's it. Um, but that's in a different album. So, it's safe to say all the English lyrics are my own.
So all the English lyrics are my own.
And then for Japanese lyrics, I basically tell the lyricists what I want it to be about and give them my lyrics too, so they know what to write about.
For Japanese lyrics, I tell the lyricists what I want.
But yeah, so it's full of my thoughts and my feelings. I'm going to put this—I really don't need to keep holding this.
It's full of my thoughts and feelings.
And this time it's a bit darker, a bit more emotional, but you guys know that I have a lot of emotions inside of me,
It's a bit darker, a bit more emotional.
and I feel like the best way to deal with those is to put them out in the world in like a productive way. I love Shuuen.
and putting them out in a productive way. I love Shuuen.
Shuuen, "last train," that's what it means in Japanese.
Shuuen means "last train" in Japanese.
I can't wait to talk more about that song too. That's also very close to my heart, that song.
That song is very close to my heart.
Um, I want to say so much more, but I probably need to wrap it up. Amazing for usual. Thank you. That's nice, I dig it. Thank you so much.
Amazing as usual, thank you, I dig it!
The lyrics are all amazing. Thank you, Deadbeat. I appreciate—I appreciate all of you. Thank you.
Thank you, Deadbeats, I appreciate all of you.
Well, we have we have some more to do here, so I can't go on forever.
We have more to do, so I can't go on forever.
It's very long MC. So, let's do another henshin and ikuzo!
It's a long MC. Let's do another henshin, ikuzo!
So look backward, look forward
Find something you can move to
Don't look back, look forward
Don't look back
I slipped in the phone and kept on looking for something to bring me up
I slipped in the phone, kept on looking for something to bring me up,
Hoping it'll gas me, no so-called singer's hope
Only tears now are drops
Walked a thin ice and it shattered a piece
It's more than a reach, it's seen so my chances decreased
Hit this a winner, but cynical as I just might be
A rant and still unwritten, I think I'm about to break free
My limits closing around me, the sound and less and less real
Because my heart is beating louder than the fear that I feel
The mind's already made, not afraid of unrealistic dream
Looking for my scream team, so I can walk on water
Used to look for perfection, now it's progress
Every dues paid, part of process
Spend this moment, maybe it's our last
Not knowing if I never try
Changing faces, wrapped all dead moonlights, I can see the stars now
Running through an endless sky
I can see the stars now
Spend this moment, if you only knew
Don't look back, look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
I fight another day, these battles inside and outside
Have all that I wanted, why am I still unsatisfied?
Lost taxis and street signs, the city mirror in my mind, alleyways to levels to forever defined
Get the world to claim me, I was always dope, but they were like 'nah'
Now it's up to me to rise, make them little surprise
My mind never slides, always riding high, thrive on this lovely hate, my new disguise
Running on my shadow, still I worn out shoes, with everything to gain, even more to give up and lose
This time you got to choose, no excuse, tired of sleeping, gotta move
Envision tomorrows that are too good to refuse
Rath of scars, waiting, but I lost my aim, more things change, but more they're still the same
Burning strife and shame, this pain will be my stress-stain
And this moment, maybe it's our last
Not knowing if I never try
Changing faces, wrapped all dead moonlights, I can see the stars now
Spend this moment, maybe it's our last
Not knowing if I never try
Changing faces, wrapped all dead moonlights, I can see the stars now
Running through an endless sky
I can see the stars now, guiding me to find for this moment
We're no longer broken, never leaving love behind
This morning, I wake up to sunrise, living with resolve now, running with a fearless stride
Give one moment for you to live how to your worth...
Don't look back, look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
晴れたって君がダメなら
Even if it's sunny, if you're no good,
花咲いた明日は雨
tomorrow, where flowers bloom, will be rain.
なせば成るなんだば惜しめのないPain
Where there's a will there's a way, no painful regrets,
忘れないのさ星まわりさ
never forgetting our stars' alignment.
目指すチャプター暗闇よもっとその燃料をよこせよ
Aiming for the chapter of darkness, give me more fuel—
今世紀最大の新境地
this century's greatest frontier!
木の穴駆け抜けた聖空にInfinity
Running through the tree's hollow, into the sacred sky, infinity—
鍵閉めて本当の魅力を
unlock your true charm!
情動思考消去しても仕様がねえ
Even if I erase my emotional thoughts, it's no use;
立ち往生して泣いちゃいねえし
I'm not standing still and crying.
乾いた牙でトライルックバックのPain
With dry fangs, try looking back at the pain—
この花は終わりにしねえ 変えなくちゃ 信じてトライ Try 泣き言拭い去って 残されたのさいっそ
I won't let these flowers end; I've gotta change, believe and try, try!
散ってよ all of songs, all of near to say 抱えきれない that I'll still sing anyway
Scatter, all of songs, all of near to say, more than I can hold, but I'll still sing anyway!
サローフォーガス デューイ ライロ ノモア シン
Sorrow forgotten, dew-ey, dry-low, no more sin...
褪せたオーネーション 出逢い直して ノーモア セイング
Faded carnation, meeting again, no more saying...
フェイドアウトはねえ 死んでもイエス エターナルアイディー
No fading out, even in death, yes, eternal ID!
焦げ付くほどのホールド ユーアー ユアーズ アンド
Scorching hold, you are yours and...
ハロー ハロー 今宵のデイリー メイン レッツ メインテイ
Hello, hello, tonight's daily main, let's maintain!
I put my last delusions behind
still, you’re creeping through my thoughts tonight
now, I know it’s only skin deep
drawn like moths to flame inside your heat, heat, heat
considered myself fine, but I’m crossing every line
drunk on love that’s not mine
heaven sent you way too late, kiss of death and take the bait
past lies and loaded dice, white lies and alibis
fingers tracing edge of sin, a medicine I never swallowed right
still no enemy to fight, not in this light
stolen whispers, don’t ask and don’t tell
step in my world, and welcome to hell
sinking down in your deep black
we fall, we break, we drown in fire
lost inside in this dark desire
no love, no faith, just you and I
dancing ‘til the end of time, la-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la
la-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la
I still blame myself for this hate
shame that overflows and never dissipates
I let words unsaid rot slowly, tainted and unholy
no, don’t say it, watch, wait
cold steel pressed against your neck
end of time, end of time, end of time
one last breath before we die
the sight of you intoxicates
say your prayers, passed the time to confess
it’s a game we never planned on winning
take us to rest, ah
six feet under, side by side
we fall, we break, we drown in fire
lost inside in this dark desire
no love, no faith, just you and I, dancing ‘til the end of time
ashes fall from blackened skies
all that’s left is you and I
drunk inside this love that’s not mine
la-la-la-la-la-la, la-la-la, end of time
Hey, yeah, hey, hello, minna-san! Woo!
Hey, yeah, hey, hello everyone! Woo!
How was that? Tenshu and Mercy!
You know, writing that song reminded me, yes, I still can write songs
that are extremely difficult to perform live.
Let's go!
Some things never changed, deadbeats.
Some things never change, deadbeats.
But hey, how about the tech for this concert? Hold on.
Are you guys seeing this Sakura behind me?
Like, the detail? Oh, hold on. Sorry, again.
The Sakura tree is very powerful! It's such a big item and so detailed!
Sometimes I stop moving. That's okay, it doesn't matter. Woo! Batch, batch, batch!
Sometimes I stop moving. That's okay, it doesn't matter. Woo!
That was a thousand out of ten, nailed it. Let's go.
Arigatou gozaimasu! It is clean.
Thank you very much! It is clean.
Drink water. That's a really good idea.
Mizu, mizu, mizu, daijoubu, daijoubu. The invisible water!
Water, water, water, it's fine. The invisible water!
But, I mean, if you guys think back to, to Phantom,
But, I mean, if you guys think back to Phantom,
I see a lot of you guys talking about, oh, the production, the quality is so crazy.
I see a lot of you guys talking about how the production and quality are so crazy.
There's very powerful stuff going on around here and they really knocked it out of the park with this.
I just have so much thanks to give to my staff.
Be sure we have a little credit roll at the end that will play and you know, that's my staff and big ups to them.
Be sure we have a little credit roll at the end that will play for my staff. Big ups to them.
But remember the Phantom concert, you guys, that we did the little mini-live for the release of Phantom, which was really cool?
Remember the Phantom concert, the little mini-live we did for the release of Phantom, which was really cool?
That already had like the echoes of the beginning of even better quality for these shows, right?
That already had the echoes of the beginning of even better quality for these shows, right?
Well, can you imagine what the next is going to look like?
I mean, if this, if this looks like this right now, I mean, can you imagine where we go from here?
I mean, if this looks like this right now, can you imagine where we go from here?
I mean, it's just really exciting to think about. 20 years from now, Deadbees, 20 years from now, who knows?
It's just really exciting to think about. 20 years from now, Deadbeats, who knows?
I probably will be as detailed as that Sakura tree, but, but, but don't worry, it won't be too much.
I probably will be as detailed as that Sakura tree, but don't worry, it won't be too much.
It'll still feel like me. I'll make sure about that. This is already kind of towing the line, I think.
It'll still feel like me. I'll make sure of that. This is already kind of towing the line, I think.
But I'd love to like move my face a little bit more and stuff like that.
But I'd love to move my face a little bit more and stuff like that.
It would be more dramatic if leaves were scattering around. That's a good point! However, Deadbeat, you say that,
It would be more dramatic if leaves were scattering around. That's a good point! However, Deadbeats, you say that,
if Sakura was falling right now, I think that I think that every PC in this studio would catch on fire.
if Sakura was falling right now, I think every PC in this studio would catch on fire.
Great idea, though. Jiro yori taimu.
Okay, here we go. Now I'm using this camera again. Woah, okay.
You guys can get I'm backing up. I'm backing up. A bit of a closer look.
You guys can get—I'm backing up. I'm backing up a bit of a closer look.
That that Sakura tree behind, that's that is three. Hold on. I got I got this.
That Sakura tree behind, that's—that is 3D. Hold on, I got this.
They're laughing. They're laughing. You're laughing at me! Stop it! Stop!
They're laughing. You're laughing at me! Stop it! Stop!
Someday I'll be able to make an angrier face at you, so get ready for that.
talking to you
Ooh, check out my nails.
You even cats hide their claws. (Claws!)
Hey.
This is a cute little screenshot, too.
I heard from my P-son, my P-son showed a little piece of paper to me that said that
#DisasterShow entered, entered the trends in USA.
Thank you so much for that.
Deadbeats, keep it coming, and some folks are like,
"Mori, I can't believe that this is free."
Of course it's free, cuz I know, I know that the majority of you guys bought the album, so might as well be free.
Um, and if you didn't buy it, you at least have been streaming it, so it just, it feels, it just feels right,
I guess, to do, uh, what I can to make it worth it to you guys, um, even more, even more so.
Hi, you guys remember this outfit?
It's a little on the older side, but check it out, you guys remember, right, from my very first solo show,
New Underworld Order?
It's looking good, right?
I'm looking good?
Hi.
Hi. Trying to get as much camera screen time as I can.
Buy the album, buy the album, say the deadbeats,
"Onegaishimasu."
If you could, I'd be very happy.
Whoa, this is kind of a cool shot with the sakura.
My eyes are glowing in the darkness. Hey there.
Hi.
Whoa! (Laughs)
I'll keep trying to make silly faces though, that's something that'll never change about me.
This is a screenshot moment.
Whenever it stops, it means it's a screenshot moment, maybe.
Anyway, it's time to move on because I still have a couple songs, uh, to sing for you guys.
I think this one will end up being longer than Phantom I'm, which is a good thing.
Um, I get to sing even more for you.
What songs will they be?
I wonder.
Arigatou, staff-san.
And, uh, yeah, so I guess it's about time that we move on to the next spot.
Looking good.
Thanks, Deadbeats. You want to see my high kicks? I've been working on them.
Oissh-ah!
And...
My high kicks.
Oissh-ah!
Next year I'm going to kick even higher, you'll see.
Uh, anyway, that was some randomness right there.
Let's go...
next...
Henshin!
Ikuzo!
I put my last delusions behind,
still you're creeping through my thoughts tonight.
Now I know it's only skin deep,
drawn like moth to flame inside your heat.
Heat.
Considered myself fine,
but I'm crossing every line.
Drunk on love that's not mine.
Heaven sent you way too late,
kiss of death and take the bait.
Past lives and loaded dice,
white lies and alibis.
Fingers tracing edge of sin,
a medicine I never swallowed right.
Still no enemy to fight, not in this light.
Stolen whispers, don't ask and don't tell,
step in my world, welcome to hell.
Sinking down in your deep black,
we fall,
we break,
we drown in fire,
lost inside this dark desire.
No love,
no faith,
just you and I,
dancing 'til the end of time.
I still blame myself for this hate,
shame that overflows - and never dissipates.
I let words unsaid rot slowly,
tainted and unholy.
No, don't say it,
watch, wait,
cold steel pressed against your neck,
one last breath before we die.
The sight of you intoxicates,
say your prayers, past the time to confess.
It's a game we never planned on winning,
take us to rest, ah.
Six feet under, side by side,
we fall,
we break,
we drown in fire,
lost inside this dark desire.
No love,
no faith,
just you and I,
dancing 'til the end of time.
Ashes fall from blackened skies,
all that's left is you and die.
Drunk inside this love that's not mine,
end of time.
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though
My heart's beating to your song (Oh yeah)
Thinking hurry up Orpheus, time's a-wasting
(Show me what you really wanna do!)
Another late night, aimless dreaming
The day-to-day starts to call
Still got like a million deadlines
Still bleeding red wine
My back up against the wall
I got my headphones on, walk home is long
Dragging feet like I'm born to lose
'Til somehow they're tapping along
To you-know-who's song
A melody I can't refuse
I'm outta line, but it's fine, you don't know my name
Safe inside my own mind, I don't feel the shame, okay?
I know I get a little carried away
But we got music when there aren't any words to say!
Cuz in my heart, feel a spark when you look this way
Gimme a sign from the stage when you feel the same
Now I'm in distress, you got me possessed, I might be obsessed,
So let me get a little something off my chest
Look, I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though
My heart's beating to your song (Oh yeah)
Thinking hurry up Orpheus, time's a-wasting
(Show me what you really wanna do!)
Tonight, it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can't see what I can see
You're gonna wind up a star
You got me dancing so bizarre
This distance got me feeling fonder, I wonder if it's enough
Cuz I'm not lying when I'm implying you're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional
Baby, this could be real love?
Give me one chance and I'll take
You make me dance the night away
Now it's a game that I've played before
But with the way the scene changed there is nothing you can blame me for
I'm talking TV screens, magazines, seen you in a couple dreams
Pictures up on every padded wall and floor
You're always talking 'bout “no time to desire a lover”
You're always talking 'bout "no time to desire a lover"
So, why'd you paint your nails up in my favorite color?
I got an attitude
Just when it comes to you
So yeah reality is kinda slipping out of tune
I'm never lost in the groove of somebody new
If it's devotion you're after, I'm staying true
So are you noticing me noticing you noticing me?
No disillusion but there's not a lot of guarantee
Cuz in my heart, feel a spark when you look this way
Gimme a sign from the stage when you feel the same
You're strumming next to me
Now I'm in ecstasy
And for the rest of the week I'm depression free
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though
My heart's beating to your song (Oh yeah)
Thinking hurry up Orpheus, time's a-wasting
(Show me what you really wanna do!)
Tonight, it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
So just as long as you keep playing that guitar…
So just as long as you keep playing that guitar...
Yeah!!
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can't see what I can see
You're gonna wind up a star!!!
You got me dancing so bizarre
This distance got me feeling fonder, I wonder if it's enough
Cuz I'm not lying when I'm implying you're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional
Baby, this could be real love!
Give me one chance and I'll take
You make me dance the night away
(Orpheus get me going
take me to space with the bass and 情熱)
So let's blow this joint
And if the feeling's right
Then we can make a little music of our own tonight, come on
(Orpheus get me going
take me to space with the bass and 情熱)
Why you walking away?
I got a lot to say!
Guess I'll save it for the next one
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess though
My heart's beating to our song (Oh yeah)
So hear me out Orpheus, thinking next time
I'll show you what I really wanna do!
I'm back, Dead Beats! Where the cats go?
Heh, hey, wait a minute. Where the weird cats at?
They were just here a second ago.
Dead Beats, check out what I can do, hold on. Get ready.
Are you ready? Check it out.
I'm obsessed with how this dress moves! Dead Beats!
I'm obsessed with— let me back up a little bit.
Look at how it moves!
Ooh, so scandalous.
Ah, don't look. The physics are crazy.
How about those weird cats though?
Doing the dance. It was so cute.
The creature, nice moves.
Thank you. Thank you Deadbeats.
Oh, that was fun. That was fun, Deadbeats.
I had such a good time with you guys today.
Actually, I mentioned to you guys my family...
My family came to glorious Nepal and actually we kind of celebrated the release together.
I was like, you know, sneaking around some places that were selling the album,
and then hearing my own music blasting on the speakers, they were playing Orpheus, they were playing Golden Balance, they were playing Let's Just Crash, and for the first time ever
Deadbeats, walking around the store, I didn't feel like embarrassed,
which is a step in the the right direction. I feel like I've been getting better, Deadbeats, I hope it was fun.
Which is a step in the right direction. I feel like I've been getting better, Deadbeats. I hope it was fun.
It was so fun. Deadbeats, I can't even explain,
being able to be so proud and say, 'Look, that's my thing, they're playing my song on the speaker.' It's so cool.
I mean, I went to karaoke with my little sister. She's told me that 'Die For You' is her favorite song of mine and 'Meta Meta', which made me very happy.
Those are little sister Reep's favorites, and I sang the I sang it for her and her friends, because they really wanted to hear, and they're like, 'Whoa, free concert!'
Those are little sister Reep's favorites, and I sang it for her and her friends, because they really wanted to hear, and they're like, 'Whoa, free concert!'
It was really cool.
So, yeah, there there was that. What else did I want to talk about? I don't know.
So, yeah, there was that. What else did I want to talk about? I don't know.
I feel like even today with with today's show, I feel like I'm getting more confident to do more things with my voice, and I can do more things with my voice.
I feel like even today with today's show, I feel like I'm getting more confident to do more things with my voice, and I can do more things with my voice.
It's still a little rough and unpolished, but like that's the point of Disaster Peace in general, right?
I'm working towards my masterpiece, and maybe um it will take some time to get things exactly the way that I want. Maybe I'll never get there, you know?
But I'm doing more with my voice, and even though it's new stuff and it needs polishing, um I'm really happy with it.
What's What's my favorite song? asked the Deadbeats.
What's my favorite song? asked the Deadbeats.
I don't know. I like them for different reasons. The one of them that maybe I'm proudest of is maybe Rivals and Equals,
'cause I still I listened to that and I'm like, 'Yeah, that's really good.' But then I also really like Shoot In for the lyrics as well.
Probably my favorite lyrics I've written in a long time.
So, yeah, that's right. That Deadbeats is is about the journey. Exactly.
So, yeah, that's right. That Deadbeats is about the journey. Exactly.
I'm running out of time here, so let me get this Jidori camera really quick. Hold on.
Ah, yes. My eyes are glowing in the dark right now because we're in a dark area, but
Ah, yes. My eyes are glowing in the dark right now because we're in a dark area.
Now I'm going to show you the skirt movement. Let's get on the red. Can I get on the red?
Now I'm going to show you the skirt moving... Let's get on the red. Can I get on the red?
Okay, I'm moving my my chest, my chest piece, which is myself to the red. Look at the skirt. It's kind of hard to see.
Sorry. Sorry. Doing my best over here. And maybe it's maybe it's better to view from the other side.
Sorry. Sorry. Doing my best over here. Maybe it's maybe it's better to view from the other side.
So, look, there's this this is the stage from Die For You MV, and then you can see if we look this way,
So look, this is the stage from the 'Die For You' MV, and then you can see if we look this way,
it's darkness, and then if we look this way, it's darkness.
But it's still really cool. Whoa, what's that?
It kind of looks like the wall that maybe leads to the hospital. I don't know. Respectfully, of course.
Peace. It's so it's so dark in here.
Peace. Peace. I'll I'll make it work. Hi. Hello.
It is I, Mori Calliope, and I just released a new album. It's my best work so far.
And in Japan, we got number one uh album on the on iTunes ranking. Yay! For alternative, for alternative music.
And in Japan, we got number one album on the iTunes ranking. Yay! For alternative, for alternative music.
So let's see how much further we can push. Last time I checked, in US, it was it was climbing. It was getting high up. But you know, there's less stiff competition there. So so all good.
So let's see how much further we can push. Last time I checked, in the US, it was climbing. It was getting high up. But you know, there's less stiff competition there. So all good.
If we don't if we don't reach number one, that's fine. But I'd love for you guys to keep pushing for me,
If we don't reach number one, that's fine. But I'd love for you guys to keep pushing for me,
uh if you would like to spread the the word and keep listening in all your favorite places,
if you would like to spread the word and keep listening in all your favorite places.
Keep enjoying the album, and I will keep making I'll keep doing stuff that only I can do, like writing more Calliope lyrics.
So, yeah, I guess that's about it. I want to give a special thanks to Deadbeats and to staff song. Itsumo arigatou gozaimasu.
So, yeah, I guess that's about it. I want to give a special thanks to Deadbeats and to staff. Itsumo arigatou gozaimasu.
My staff is the best. Please look at the credits so you know who to say thank you too.
My staff is the best. Please look at the credits so you know who to say thank you to.
Deadbeats, uh and yeah, posted everywhere. Thank you. Thank you Deadbeat.
Deadbeats, and yeah, posted everywhere. Thank you. Thank you, Deadbeats.
I'm reading y'all comments to eat the camera. I think that's a bad idea. I think they'll get mad at me if I do that.
I think I think it's going to it's going to break things. So, anyway, that's the end of the Jidori camera.
I think I think it's going to break things. So, anyway, that's the end of the Jidori camera.
Um, anyway, we are back here. So, I guess that's oh, like I said, I'm using a headset. No, no, no, really microphone, trust, trust.
Um, but you know, the with the technical stuff, there's always a little bit of magic involved, right, in order to get the level of quality that we've got.
Um, but you know, with the technical stuff, there's always a little bit of magic involved, right, in order to get the level of quality that we've got.
So, um, thank you guys always for cheering for me and being excited about my work.
Now, there is no encore because life has no encore. So, sorry about that.
I think there are a lot of songs you guys want to hear me sing. The good news is I will be singing them soon for you on my streams.
like my karaoke streams and streams where I'm singing my stuff
and uh future shows, if there's a song that you really want to hear, like I know a lot of you probably want to hear Shouten, for example. So,
and future shows. If there's a song you really want to hear—like I know a lot of you probably want to hear Shouten, for example—so,
if you want to hear it, you got to stay tuned and come to the next one.
if you want to hear it, you gotta stay tuned and come to the next one.
Like I said, life has no encore.
So, um what I want you to do now is just rewatch the live
So, what I want you to do now is just rewatch the live
and then go listen to the music. Links in the description.
Thank you Deadbeats always for cheering for me.
Thank you for supporting what I do.
I'm strange, but you know, this is really fun.
I'm glad I get to do this every day,
and I put my whole heart into the new release. So,
I'll see you guys tomorrow. We're playing a game.
There's there's a game stream tomorrow.
There's a game stream tomorrow.
See you guys around. Thanks again, everyone.
I'm your Mori, hope you'll remember me.
Peace.
Dead Beats!! Much love to you.
Thank you for following your (at times) disaster (affectionate) of an oshi.
Let's keep chasing our own masterpieces. Even if we're imperfect, even if we fail every time.
That is to live, I think.
So many late nights, times are wastin', tell me what you really wanna do
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be, sometimes it feels
like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
critics so loud, so predictable
they can't see what I can see, girl
hey! you got eyes and ears,
but you don't look or listen!
in other words, you're useless,
every last one of ya!
i'm just the type you'd forget so
don't waste your time!
let's just crash
不確かな物語に 勝ち取るはアイデンティティー
Winning the uncertain story is our identity,
あれやこれやと 手を替え品を替え
trying this and that, changing means and methods.
2人ならやれるさ back-to-back, no matter what
If we're together, we can do it, back-to-back, no matter what.
背負ったもん武器に変わる spot
The spot where what we've carried turns into a weapon.
we fall, we break,
we drown in fire,
lost inside this dark desire
no love, no faith, just you and i
未知なる未来のマーシーマーシー
The mercy, mercy of an unknown future...
この街にしかないの愛を
The love that only exists in this town.
強がり笑って見せるわ 私が迷う夜を独り
I'll put on a brave smile on nights I get lost alone,
歩いて 私が迷う
walking as I get lost.
when thunder crashes down
when the world caves under my pressure, there'll be no one to save
めくるめく 運命に逆らって
Spinning around, defying destiny,
出会い想いを通わせた
meeting and connecting our thoughts.
the strangers i followed with stars in my eyes
さぁゃきっと待ち望んで
Come on, surely waiting and wanting,
欲しがっている someone 誰にも届かない longing chain
wanting someone, a longing chain that reaches no one.
i can't be someone else,
despite it all my mind has become my hell
with no escape or hope in the dark
but still in my heart your words echo over and over
暗くなる頃始まるパーティー集める人種は様々
A party starting as it gets dark, various kinds of people gathering,
フラフラするでしょう クラクラ来るでしょう ホロホロとろけそう そうでしょ う flash bang
you'll probably feel unsteady, get dizzy, about to melt away, right? Flash bang!
in this moment maybe it's hopeless
not knowing if i never try
遠い日の夢を見る度 生まれた意味を考えてしまうのさ
Every time I see a dream of distant days, I end up thinking about the meaning of being born.
謳歌 美しい青い日々だな
Oh, beautiful blue days...
we fall, we break,
we drown in fire,
lost inside this dark desire
no love, no faith, just you and i